Name: Neha Jamadar Mob No.: +91 9075913301

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

#### > SYNOPSIS

4.5+ years of IT experience in Functional Testing and Non-Functional Testing – **Automation** (Selenium WebDriver), Manual **& Quality Assurance**. Seeking a challenging and exciting career where currency are ideas, smart work with rigorous thinking and boundless curiosity.

#### > TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools	Selenium WebDriver, Bitbucket, Bitrise
Other Tools	Eclipse, Jira, qTest, TMS
Frameworks	TestNG, Data Driven Development, Page Object Model
Languages known	Java, SQL
Functional Area	Core Banking, Retail Banking, Telecom
Operating System	Windows / iOS / Android

## **EDUCATION**

B.E. Information Technology from North Maharashtra University, Jalgaon

## **CERTIFICATION**

Diploma in Software Testing from SEED Infotech

#### > EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Netcracker Technology, Pune Designation: Test Automation Engineer  Current Project: Rakuten Mobile – Telecom domain (May 2022 – till date)		
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Majorly involved into test case migration activities</li> <li>Analyze the execution flow and run automated test cases</li> <li>Test case script fixing as per requirement and flow</li> <li>Using Jira defect management tool for defect reporting and tracking</li> </ul>	

Name: Neha Jamadar Mob No.: +91 9075913301

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

Infosys Limited, Pune Designation: Test Engineer			
Current Project: Ally Bank – Banking domain (Apr 2021 – May 2022)			
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Web and Mobile Automation, Jira, qTest		
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Execute test cases manually at the time of Regression Testing</li> <li>Test case management using qTest</li> <li>Identify candidate for automation Testcases and develop the test scripts.</li> <li>Used Bitrise platform to manage application binaries</li> <li>Executed the Test suite run on automation suites in BrowserStack</li> <li>Automated test scripts for different platforms like iOS, Android</li> <li>Defect Reporting and tracking using Jira</li> <li>Contributed into other teams for UI validation</li> </ul>		

INNsight Interactive, Mumbai Designation: QA Analyst		
Previous Project: Hospitality domain project (Sep 2019 – Apr 2021)		
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Selenium, Java, Web Automation	
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement specifications</li> <li>Identify and write the test cases in excel</li> <li>Manual Test case execution on web and mobile application</li> <li>Performed Cross browser Testing</li> <li>Automated test scripts for Web application and websites, using Selenium WebDriver</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect tracking using Jira</li> </ul>	

Name: Neha Jamadar Mob No.: +91 9075913301

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

Xinet Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Nashik Designation: QA Engineer		
Previous Project: Seller Overview		
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Jira	
Responsibilities:	<ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement Specification</li> <li>Identify and write the test scenarios and test cases in Excel.</li> <li>Performed Functional and non-functional testing</li> <li>Worked on Web Application aspects and UI Testing</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification</li> </ul>	

## > STRENGTHS

- Capable of Quick learning and delivering solutions as an individual and as part of a team
- Good analytical skills, presentation skills with good communication skills
- self-starter and consistent performer
- Result oriented, self-driven, highly motivated, smart, and hungry to learn new technologies, methodologies, strategies, and processes.

# **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Marital Status: Unmarried
 Hobbies: Singing, Dancing
 Date of birth: 16<sup>th</sup> May 1995

• Permanent address: Khanderao Pada, Thalner, Tal. Shirpur, Dist. Dhule, 425421